Okay, another way you can fix an error is...kind of goes back to not making it in the first place.
And one of the ways that I find that I make less and less errors, is I'm more comfortable where I'm at in my studio.
And I have a nice set-up where I work.
I have music that I listen to, and things like that.
What happens is, there's less stress.
And if....if you're in a peaceful place, and it's less stress, and you're doing what you love to do, you're probably not going to make as many mistakes.
So if you're prone to painting at the kitchen table while you're cooking dinner and the kids are running in and out of the house, and the husband's not home yet, might not...you might make some errors and you might not be able to fix them.
But if you can find a nice, secluded place where you can actually paint, and be by yourself, and be comfortable where you're at, you won't make as many errors because you're going to be more relaxed.
And if you do make an error, it'll be much easier to fix, and you just won't be all stressed out.
So, definitely, be happy where you paint, and you will make a lot fewer mistakes.
So, that's one of my secrets, and I hope it works for ya.